To create insurance from this Earth, first of all
we have to type in the URL
digitalseva.ac.gov.in. Its
interface will be something like this.
Here we will enter our user ID and password and then we will scroll
down. The
dashboard of Avani CID is like this.
In this you can see that there are
some icons. Click on the insurance icon and
join the motor
third party. There are some
companies in it for creating insurance, from
which we will select one company, for
example, I
want to create insurance from ICICI Lombard General Insurance,
so click on Hair Pack. Its
interface is something like this, for example,
here
I want to create third party insurance for two wheeler and two wheeler profession,
so I will click on two wheeler TV. It is
[music] that there are
some details here and we have to fill up,
like in the first
registration number, we will fill up our vehicle number here
and click on Get Out, this retail pack.
After clicking on this, some date gets
automatically filled, like
RTO First Registration Number, Customer
Statement for Watching Model  If you select the policy start
date for which you want to create an appointment, then you are going to
select it, you are going to scroll
down a bit, click here and
flip through the details like engine number, chassis
number, type, year, these details are also automatically filled, you will add a
little more of it,
like I will fill up the nominee details here,
nominee name, nominee
for operation and nominee HA,
I will first click on Get Court, the
total premium amount in the previous thank you is
Rs 828
and the quota ID has been generated here,
hello friends, I will fill up the details
Ajay, to
create a new customer,
here you have to flip through the customer details,
like the first title
was customer name,
father's name, address, pin code,
email ID, mobile number, state, whatever it is, we will fill them up
[music],
like I have given these details,
click on Get Proposal,
like proposal ID and in this way
click on Buy Policy, to do police bike, click on the
password of your CSC ID here
And as it is given
above that the amount i.e. 80, sorry, we have to do it
last, we will
pin the wallet,
click here,
after clicking on this the amount will be
debited from our account,
as if the payment has been successful
[music]
and here you can see, here the
policy number,
how much is this cream, politics start
date, politician and
click on the speed effect present in A, then
its PDF has been generated,
we save it on the desktop, do it,
now after printing it we can give it to the customer, in
this way friends we
can make insurance from CSC, so like,
share and subscribe to the channel and do not
forget to click on the bell icon because
friends whenever I give information about CSC Mitra computer
technology and various schemes, then
you will get that information
first through notification. See you
in the next video
with the next topic. Till then, thank you,
thank you.